This is Deadly Queen.
I bestowed it with a moniker myself. Hmph.
I'm only telling you
because you're going to die.
After you bite the dust, I'll
be able to sleep soundly.
Hey, didn't I warn you not
to make a move against me?
You're about to learn
that I mean business!
Yes!
Well now, color me surprised.
I crushed several of these vermin,
yet you remain completely unscathed.
This is your last chance, pal.
Move again and I'll slice whatever
that big artery is in your neck.
Oh yeah, now I remember.
It's called the carotid artery.
You move a muscle, and I'll have my
invincible harvest hack it to pieces.
Judging by the look of
that stand of yours,
it pecks a wallop if you're up close, but
it's really shitty when it comes down?
long-range fighting.
If I had to guess, I'd say it's got
a range of one, maybe two meters.
So go ahead and make your move,
if you're ready to die, that is.
Fascinating.
From the looks of things, it seems each
user is endowed with a unique ability.
Stand.
I believe that's the term you used.
I should tell you,
as far as special abilities go, Deadly
Queen has one that puts others to shame.
Hmm?
What's that in its hand?
Grab it, Harvest!
That's weird.
It's just a normal 100 yen coin.
What the heck were you
planning to do with this?
Simple.
I was going to reveal what makes Deadly
Queen such a unique and terrifying stand.
There's no point in keeping its powers
secret when you're already as good as dead.
Deadly Queen has an astonishing power.
Any object that it touches becomes an
explosive that rips its target asunder.
That's right, even something as
simple as a hundred yen coin.
Quick harvest!
You have to let go of the coin right now!
That didn't take long.
Now a night of glorious sleep awaits.
Thank you.
I love you, so I love you!
Wait a second.
My face is...
What happened to me?
I told you.
Deadly Queen has the ability to transform
anything it touches into a bomb.
That's what it was doing when you
asked about this hundred-yen coin.
I press the detonator whenever the
urge hits me, and once it's triggered,
my victim is blown to
smithereens from the inside out.
Though in your case, Shigechi,
it appears the blast partially
imploded your malformed face?
Leaving behind a stomach-churning cocktail
of facial fascia and cerebral tissue!
Before I deliver the blow
that ends your wretched life.
There's something of great
importance I must ask you.
Earlier you referred to
this power as a stand.
Do the others, Josuke and Okuyasu,
also wield the power of the stand?
I don't want to die
here, somebody help me,
Your death is a necessity at this point.
Now that you know my secret,
I can't let you live.
It's nothing personal,
but I can't allow a single living soul to
know the true nature of Yoshikage Kira.
Though I must admit, I find myself
fascinated by these stand users.
I could figure this out on my own,
but I'd rather use the fleeting
resource that lies before me.
Josuke, Okuyasu, who are
the others besides them?
How many users are residing in this town?
What are their powers?
Don't know.
Just let me go. Please.
Come now.
I'm sure you know more
than you're letting on.
And if you refuse to tell me, your
parents will pay for it with their lives.
What?
No, you can't.
I won't let you hurt my mommy and daddy.
Well, I won't have to if you hurry up
and give me the answers I'm looking for.
Now quit your stalling.
I need to slip away before anyone sees me.
Just the names will do.
Hop to it, boy.
Hang on.
Everyone says there was a
murderer in this town and
they're all trying to track
him down before he kills again.
It's all making sense now.
The killer they were talking about is you.
You messed up son of a bitch.
You killed Reimi Sugimoto too. What?
How do you know that girl?
The little shit can still use his stand?
This isn't good.
Deadly queen!
That brat.
I was so close to killing him.
I managed to give him the slip.
Now I just have to get to Josuke.
Once I make it there, he can use
his shining diamond to fix me.
There's no way I'm going to
sit back and die like this.
No matter what, I'll protect
my mommy and my daddy.
I promise I'll fight to keep them
safe from this hand-hoarding monster.
That horrible creep is rotten to the core.
And I'd rather die than let them live
in the same town as my mommy and daddy.
I have to find Josuke.
If he heals me, I can save him.
Sorry about that.
Hey, kid, you're not hurt, are you?
I have to find him.
Gee, I wonder what's the
matter with the little guy.
I don't know, but he looks
like a middle School.
Oh, no.
Something's wrong with him.
Let's see if we can find a teacher.
We should leave him be.
He's kind of weird.
Come on.
Josuke!
I recall you said something
about people looking for me.
Does that mean there's
someone else here who
knows the truth about
Reimi Sugimoto's murder?
Even if there is, they won't
be able to track me down.
The fact remains, no one knows
Yoshikage Kira's true colors.
It's a secret you'll have to carry
with you all the way to the grave.
No!
I'm gonna protect Mommy!
Sorry, but Deadly Queen has already
left its mark on the doorknob.
Behold the genius of my Deadly Queen.
All evidence of my true
self has been destroyed.
Hey, did you hear someone
call my name just now?
Yeah, most definitely.
Josuke, you seeing what I'm seeing?
I got it.
No, Shigechi!
Shigechi!
Hey, something's not right, Josuke.
Harvest was limping around and
bleeding before it vanished,
but that's not how a
stand usually disappears.
And why the heck would only
one of them come to see us?
Let's head over to the middle school.
We have to find Shigechi right now.
What's this?
Where could I have
possibly lost my button?
Well, it can't be helped.
I just have to visit my tailor
and hope he carries the same kind.
It can't be. Not again.
That foul demon.
He's taken another life.
Another victim screams across the skies.
Why does this keep happening?
Shigechi
There's no doubt about it.
This boy has passed.
Shigekio must have had a
run-in with the killer.
One that cost him his life.
The whole thing is sickening.
I know what you must be thinking.
How did they meet and how was he murdered?
But I have no idea.
I'm positive it was his doing.
I'd recognize the handiwork
of that murderer anywhere.
Trust me.
We just looked for Shigeki but
couldn't find him anywhere.
I still don't get how
this could have happened.
We only let him out of our
sight for five minutes.
His books and school supplies are
in the same place he left them,
and his parents have filed
a missing person report?
though I doubt anything useful
will turn up at this point.
I have to wonder.
Wait, what are you saying, Josuke?
You don't think a stand
user did this, do you?
You guys couldn't possibly know this,
but Shigechi's stand harvest was, well,
in a word, the thing was
damn near invincible.
So what the hell?
This guy killed Shigechi in five minutes.
Then he hit his body off
campus without anyone noticing.
Well, there you have it, Jotaro.
It's pretty obvious that we're
dealing with a murderous stand user.
We can't just sit by and
watch like spectators.
Hey, Josuke.
You said you found a button, right?
Oh, yeah.
Harvest brought it to me
before falling to pieces.
Here you go.
This is Shigechi's dying message.
It's very likely Harvest
pulled it off the murderer.
If so, we've been given an important clue.
I'd like to investigate
this thing further.
Mind if I keep it? Be my guest,
but how much information can you really
get from some run-of-the-mill button?
More than you would think.
We might find the brand of the
clothes, or even the manufacturer.
Good idea.
Hey, if we're done with this little
meeting, I think I'm gonna go home.
Talking about all this is
putting me in a weird mood.
I'm really pissed.
Come on, dad, let's go!
What's up with him?
This isn't like him at all.
Yeah, but I know how he feels.
Shigeji may have come off as
an annoying greedy bastard
but there was something
undeniably lovable about him.
I still haven't wrapped my head
around the fact that he's gone.
Honestly, I'm not sure how to feel.
I don't know whether to rage at
the world or cry my eyes out.
It's one of the most irritating
things you can imagine.
I'm sure he feels it too.
But it's probably way worse for him.
Shit!
How could something so horrific be
happening in Mariah right under my nose?
I'll make sure all my customers know
to keep an eye out for this madman.
I can't imagine he would pay me a
visit, but I'll take some precautions.
Keep in mind, stand users have a
nasty habit of finding each other.
That said, I hope we never meet.
So the time has come for
us all to take action.
Hmm?
That was definitely Josuke.
And Okuyasu is with him.
You won't believe what happened.
So you remember how it was
my birthday this past Friday?
Well, that guy I'm seeing
decided to give me a gift.
I mean, if you can even call it
that, it's just a shitty ring.
I wouldn't be caught
dead wearing this thing.
I know, but for now I have to
be like, oh my god, I love it.
Jeez, I'm only dating him
because his dad owns some land.
The guy's a total hick.
I bet if this crap is
the best he can afford.
How much did it cost?
I'm guessing like $150,000.
If you want it, I bet you
could sell it at a pawn shop.
I can't let my beautiful fingers
be sullied by such trash.
Her soul is as grotesque as they come.
But her hands and face are quite lovely.
I'd like to set her soul right
and show her a glorious time.
Well, I've got to get going.
I'll see you soon. Okay, then. Later.
Time we went our separate ways.
We had a good run, but it's over now.
Good morning, everyone, and
welcome to Mariah Radio.
This is Kai Harada, your easy-listening
disc jockey extraordinaire.
Are you ready for a magnificent week?
It's hard to believe there are
only three days left to do this.
Feel free to dig in.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I'm going to be out of the house
today running a few errands,
so I'd like you to stay put, okay?
We'll wine and dine when I get back.
How does that sound?
Thankfully, they still had some
of the Parisian specials left.
We got here in the nick of time.
Let's head over to Yohei Lake.
But Asuka's not here yet. Oh, yeah.
It's been four days since we
found out about Shigechi's murder.
It's been fairly quiet since then, but...
There's still a killer lurking
somewhere in the shadows of this town.
When it comes down to it, the
mind only sees what it wants to.
The look of guilt and innocence
is in the eye of the beholder.
Oh, uh, hi there, Mr. Jotaro.
Did anything weird stick out to
you during your investigation?
You remember, right?
You said something about
examining the murderer's button?
Oh, that, not yet.
Hopefully that changes soon.
Hmm.
Yeah, it'd be a great help.
So, um, you headed anywhere in particular?
No, not really.
I'm just walking.
Oh, I see.
Son of a bitch.
Getting the strong silent type
to chat is like pulling teeth.
Rohan-sensei's pushiness is unsettling,
But Jotaro's silence sends me into a panic.
There's gotta be something
we can talk about.
Let's see.
I think that coat of yours is Bites!
Looks like we found a shoe store.
Huh?
What do you know?
It is a shoe store. Good catch.
Uh, is something wrong?
Oh.
It is a shoe store, but they
also do simple alterations.
Well, that's certainly convenient.
if anyone ever needs their skirt
waists and pants hemmed high,
know where to send them.
Plus, the electronics shop sells flowers.
What made you want to stop here?
I did a bit of digging and learned
all about the tailors of Morioh,
but it didn't occur to me till
now to ask about places like this.
Oh.
Hmm.
So, is there something
wrong with the button?
No.
If it doesn't ring a bell, forget it.
I just couldn't remember what
it was originally attached to.
That's too bad.
Hey, kid, want an animal cracker?
I got plenty.
I saved the camels for last, but
everything else is fair game,
so feel free to take
as many as you can eat.
Thanks, but no, I'm fine for now, sir.
Suit yourself.
Getting back to the point,
not only have I seen it,
believe it or not, I actually
just finished some alterations!
on the jacket that it belongs to.
A customer dropped by yesterday
and asked me to replace
a missing button with the
same kind you brought in.
See for yourselves.
They're identical.
Does this mean…
It looks that way.
We found it, Koichi.
Found what exactly? Oh, nothing.
More importantly, what did
the customer look like?
Do you recall his name?
Are you serious?
Of course I do.
What kind of businessman
would I be if I didn't?
Each and every one of my customers' names
is filed away in the old noggin here.
Anything less would just be rude
to my well-paying clientele.
I've got thousands of
names locked away in here.
You don't say.
You're absolutely incredible, sir!
Would you mind telling
us who owns that jacket?
Well, I guess helping you
out couldn't hurt nothing.
I keep the names on the order tags.
So you know, I don't need these tags.
I remember the names just fine.
But things tend to run more
smoothly when I have them on hand.
Let's see here.
Huh? That's interesting.
How do you read this last name?
It has to be...
I don't mean to rush you, sir, but
maybe I can help you figure it out?
That can't be it.
Maybe it's...
Oh!
Look over here. Ah!
Why'd my hand explode?
What the hell's going on here?
Look over here. Ah! Jotaro!
Tell me you're saying this!
Just keep your guard up, Koichi,
and don't get any closer to it.
Hey, didn't you hear me?
I said look over here.
Is that his stand?
Jotaro, look at the coat rack!
The killer is here, and he's
trying to take the jacket!
I never imagined someone
would go so far as to
investigate the button
that fell off my jacket.
What a careless mistake.
This is bad.
Have those two already seen my name?
Why have I been faced with
nothing but adversity lately?
Ah, good grief.
This would be when he
comes to get his suit.
Panicking would be a mistake.
I'll simply execute them with
Deadly Queen's Bomb Type II.
Just like that pathetic punk Shigechi.
It's moving again!
Our evidence! Wait!
We can't go blindly after it.
Look at the way he's pulling the jacket.
It's strange.
What is his power?
Watch out, it's gonna blow!
I move so slightly to
the arms and the lips and
the face of the humic and
of all that I need to.
I want to come and stand
a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you!
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you.
Ooh, I got it if I need you.
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you?
But, ooh, I'm done for now.